rust-servers.net 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Politique de Confidentialité

__Lire la Version Française

We collect only the following information for the use of " **Rust-Servers.net** ". We never sell your personal information to third parties. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [admin@rust-servers.net](mailto:admin@rust-servers.net)

**Last Revision: September 13th, 2014**

## What we collect

### User information

When you register on " **Rust-Servers.net** ", you must provide us a nickname and a valid email address. We only use these information for notices, warnings, internal newsletters, password retrieval and account activation.

**Your information will never be shared with any 3rd parties.**

### Server information

When you register a server on " **Rust-Servers.net** ", we collect all information you provide us with. By registering your server, you accept that we publicly publish some information, like your server's IP address, server port...

### Access information

Like many other websites, we make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, type of operating system, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time, referring/exit pages....

 _IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any other information that are personally identifiable_

.

### Cookies

Our Cookie policy is available here: Cookie Policy

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Third-party advertising companies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

## Other Terms

" **Rust-Servers.net** " reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy at anytime with or without notice. 

__Read English Version

Nous collectons les informations suivantes uniquement pour l'usage des services de " **Rust-Servers.net** ". Nous nous ne céderons jamais vos informations personnelles à des tiers. Si vous avez des questions à propos de notre politique de confidentialité, vous pouvez nous contacter à : [admin@rust-servers.net](mailto:admin@rust-servers.net)

**Dernière révision: September 13th, 2014**

## Informations que nous collectons

### Informations utilisateur

Lorsque vous vous enregistrez sur " **Rust-Servers.net** ", vous devez fournir un nom d'utilisateur ainsi qu'une adresse email valide. Nous utilisons uniquement ces informations pour les notifications, alertes, lettres d'information interne, réinitialisation de mot de passe et activation de compte.

**Vos informations ne seront jamais partagées ou cédées à un tiers.**

### Informations serveur

Lorsque vous vous enregistrez un serveur sur " **Rust-Servers.net** ", nous collectons toutes les informations que vous fournissez. En enregistrant votre serveur, vous acceptez que nous publions certaines informations, comme l'adresse IP de votre serveur, le numéro de port...

### Informations d'accès

Comme beaucoup de sites Internet, nous utilisons des fichiers d'historique. Les informations des fichiers d'historique inclues l'adresse IP, le type de navigateur, le type de système d'exploitation, le fournisseur d'accès Internet, la date et heure, les pages référentes...

 _L'adresse IP et les autres informations ne sont pas liées à d'autre informations personnellement identifiable_

.

### Cookies

Politique liée aux cookies est consultable ici : Politique Liée aux Cookies

## Liens vers d'autres sites

Notre site Internet peut contenir des liens vers d'autres sites Internet. Cependant, une fois que vous utilisez ces liens pour quitter notre site Internet, vous devez comprendre que nous n'avons aucun contrôle sur les autres sites. Donc nous ne sommes plus responsable de la protection et de la confidentialité des informations que vous allez fournir en visitant ces sites. Vous devez faire attention et consulter la politique de confidentialité qui s'applique au site Internet en question.

## Entreprises de publicités tierces

Nous faisons appel à des entreprises de publicités tierces pour l'affichage de publicités lors de votre visite sur notre site Internet. Ces entreprises peuvent utiliser des informations (qui n'incluent en aucun cas votre nom, adresse ou numéro de téléphone) à propos de votre visite sur ce site et d'autres sites pour vous fournir des publicités ciblées sur des produits ou services. Si vous voulez plus d'informations sur ces pratiques et connaître les possibilités pour ne pas avoir ces informations utilisées par ces entreprises, cliquez [ici](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

## Modifications

" **Rust-Servers.net** " se réserve le droit de modifier sa politique de confidentialité à tout moment avec ou sans message d'avertissement.
